javaprogrammingforums.com 2015-03-29

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguard your privacy while online at our site www.javaprogrammingforums.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Our site doesn’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners (for example, www.google.com ) use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on websites including our site www.javaprogrammingforums.com.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html   
**  
Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
**  
Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Axill, Kontera etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: sales@impactomatic.com

Go Back to [www.javaprogrammingforums.com](http://www.javaprogrammingforums.com/)
